let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which plant often given as a gift at Christmas has bright red and green leaves and is sometimes known as the Christmas flower?",
    answer: "Poinsettia",
    options: [
      "Holly",
      "Douglas Fir",
      "Mistletoe",
      "Poinsettia"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How many tips does a snowflake have?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "4",
      "6",
      "8",
      "10"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which Christmas product did Sir Henry Cole produce in 1843?",
    answer: "Christmas Cards",
    options: [
      "Christmas Cards",
      "Holly Wreath",
      "Christmas Tree",
      "Christmas Crackers"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Who is the patron saint celebrated on the 26th December?",
    answer: "Saint Stephen",
    options: [
      "Saint Patrick",
      "Saint George",
      "Saint Stephen",
      "Saint Anthony"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How long does it take for a tree to reach the average, ideal Christmas tree height?",
    answer: "15 years",
    options: [
      "15 years",
      "10 years",
      "6 months",
      "12 months"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Name the animatronic cassette-playing bear toy that every kid wanted for Christmas in the mid-80s?",
    answer: "Teddy Ruxpin",
    options: [
      "Furby",
      "Teddy Ruxpin",
      "Peek a Boo Teddy Bear",
      "Tickle Me Elmo"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which U.S. state was the first to declare Christmas an official holiday?",
    answer: "Alabama",
    options: [
      "New York",
      "California",
      "Texas",
      "Alabama"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the most recorded Christmas song of all time?",
    answer: "Silent Night",
    options: [
      "Jingle Bells",
      "Silent Night",
      "Deck the Halls",
      "Away in a Manger"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "In The Muppet Christmas Carol, who played Scrooge?",
    answer: "Michael Caine",
    options: [
      "Kermit the Frog",
      "Fozzie Bear",
      "Michael Caine",
      "Jim Carey"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who invented electric Christmas lights?",
    answer: "Thomas Edison",
    options: [
      "Thomas Edison",
      "Nikola Tesla",
      "Benjamin Franklin",
      "Alexander Graham Bell"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "How many gifts in total were given in “The Twelve Days of Christmas” song?",
    answer: "364",
    options: [
      "12",
      "144",
      "253",
      "364"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What spy hides around the house, reporting back to Santa on who has been naughty and nice?",
    answer: "Elf on the Shelf",
    options: [
      "Robin Redbreast",
      "Frosty the Snowman",
      "Elf on the Shelf",
      "Jack Skellington"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "In which century was the term Xmas coined?",
    answer: "16th",
    options: [
      "14th",
      "16th",
      "18th",
      "20th"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "What was the highest grossing Christmas movie of all time?",
    answer: "The Grinch",
    options: [
      "The Grinch",
      "Home Alone",
      "Miracle on 34th Street",
      "It's a Wonderful Life"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Is Die Hard a Christmas movie?",
    answer: "Yes",
    options: [
      "Yes",
      "Yes",
      "Yes",
      "Yes"
    ]
  },
];